<character>
<monster>
	<unlocklevel value="0">
		<boss>
			<race>boss</race>
			<story>His origin remains unclear, but according to some human survivors that he is once a legend in the human empire.
            </story>
			<description>Souls And Hearts</description>
		</boss>
<zombie>
			<race>undead</race>
			<story>The medium undead reanimated corpse shambles about in a jerky, uneven gait without fear or hesitation. Drawn from the grave, half decayed and partially consumed by worms, it wears the tattered moldering remains of its burial clothes. A rank odor of death and decay hangs heavy in the air. 
            </story>
			<description>There Is A Zombie On Your Lawn</description>
</zombie>
<sprite>
			<race>fey</race>
			<story>Sprites travel in swarms and can bite if provoked. They are playful, and at times obnoxious. One of their favorite past-times is pestering butterflies. This is a great game for them as they are able to fly much faster than butterflies and can go greater distances before requiring rest.
            </story>
			<description>The refreshing taste of lemon lime sprite Dayum dats gud</description>
</sprite>

	</unlocklevel>
	<unlocklevel value="1">
<druid>
			<race>druid</race>
			<story>Guardians of nature who seek to preserve balance and protect life, Druids have unmatched versatility on the field of battle. This is in part because druidism is much more than a fighting discipline—it’s a way of life steeped in traditions so ancient that even the origin of their kind is preserved largely in mythology passed on through millennia.
</story>
			<description>We are the preservers of the balance, now and forever</description>
</druid>
<dwarf>
			<race>humanoid</race>
			<story>The Dwarf people as a whole are sturdy and strong, brilliant craftsmen and excellent warriors, but above all they prize themselves on their loyalty to each other and to those they are indebted to.This strong bond of kinship has ensured that the Dwarfs are considered amongst the most united races in the face of the world.
            </story>
			<description>If there's one thing dwarves love, it's drinking. And fighting. Two things</description>
</dwarf>
<giant>
            <race>giant</race>
			<story>Giants are one-eyed giants that eke out a meager existence in wild lands. They are a terrifying threat in combat due to their size and strength, but they can often be tricked by clever foes.
            </story>
			<description>If your name is Noman, use a fake name</description>
</giant>
</unlocklevel>
<unlocklevel value="2">
<ghoul>
			<race>humanoid</race>
			<story>In ancient Arabic folklore, ghūls belonged to a diabolic class of jinn (spirits) and were said to be the offspring of Iblīs, the prince of darkness in Islam. They were capable of constantly changing form, but their presence was always recognizable by their unalterable sign—ass’s hooves.
            </story>
			<description>Neither man nor woman…neither brute nor human</description>
</ghoul>
<stoneman>
			<race>humanoid</race>
			<story>These creatures seem to be affected by an unknown disease. Although their origin remains mystery, the disease have changed their appearance and even inside  that the most impacted part of them is the stone-constructed body.
            </story>
			<description>A rough devil</description>
</stoneman>
<goblin>
			<race>goblinoid</race>
			<story>Their love of money, explosives, and technology leaves them to be a very dangerous race, both to their enemies and themselves. Most goblins have a neutral standpoint, preferring to sell their contraptions, knowledge and services to other races.
</story>
			<description>Clever as they come, but not the most friendly of beasts</description>
</goblin>
</unlocklevel>
<unlocklevel value="3">
<bloodseeker>
			<race>humanoid</race>
			<story>Bloodseekers feed exclusively on blood and are especially drawn to large animals, such as livestock. While solitary bloodseekers are timid beings and will flee from attackers, they are social creatures and often live in large groups referred to as clots.
</story>
			<description>Luring for blood, seeking satisfactory</description>
</bloodseeker>
<chimera>
			<race>hybrid</race>
			<story>It is said to be having a body and a head of a male lion, with the head of a goat arising from its back,  and a tail that might end with a snake head. She does not typically have the power of flight.
</story>
			<description>Self-aware creatures, with a limited capacity for language</description>
</chimera>
<bugbear>
			<race>goblinoid</race>
			<story>Bugbears, like other goblinoids, had a reputation for being dim-witted and brutish. This claim was not unfounded and like their kin bugbears had easily provoked tempers and were prone to rages. Few bugbears overcame this flaw and their culture's brutal nature.
            </story>
			<description>Like many goblinoids, bugbears spoke the Goblin language</description>
</bugbear>
</unlocklevel>
<unlocklevel value="4">
<drow>
			<race>elf</race>
			<story>Drow, by reputation, were almost entirely evil. The teachings of Lolth represented the standard moral code for most of the race. They were overall decadent but managed to hide it under a veneer of sophistication.
            </story>
			<description>The Ones Who Went Below</description>
</drow>
<centaur>
			<race>humanoid</race>
			<story>Centaurs were a strong and proud race. Although they typically strove to find peace and balance with nature, they could act with violence when the need arose. Despite this desire for balance, centaurs had to eat a lot to fuel their large bodies and were known to overindulge, especially with wine and ale.</story>
			<description>They had good relations with elves, being as they were both creatures of the forest</description>
</centaur>
<mindflayer>
			<race>humanoid</race>
			<story>The mind flayer mind knew only negative emotions, only finding fulfillment in the angry and sadistic act of consuming a brain. The closest to happiness any mind flayer could know was in its pride and in satisfying its curiosity.
            </story>
			<description>To put out the myriad suns―to darken the light</description>
</mindflayer>
</unlocklevel>
<unlocklevel value="5">
<dragon>
			<race>dragon</race>
			<story>Dragons were inherently magical beings, and in no case should dragons be considered reptiles, despite obvious similarities such as a scaled epidermis and reproduction by laying eggs.[30] In fact, they were more akin to feline creatures than reptiles, particularly in regards to their posture and movements, as well as being inherently warm-blooded and an eye composition similar to felines, although far more complex.
            </story>
			<description>Thet could cross-breed with virtually any other creature</description>
</dragon>
</unlocklevel>
</monster>
<enemy>
    <normal>
        <level value="1">
            <wanderingswordsman>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>A man of honor.
Picked up a couple tricks along the way, done what needed to be done to simply get by. He's a seasoned swordsman now, his trusty blades have served him well over the past years. Where will they take him now?
</story>
			<description>Not all those who wander are lost</description>
            </wanderingswordsman>
            <magicapprentice>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>Bein' a mage means knowin' power can flow in more than one direction. Usually in the tutelage of more powerful spellcasters, apprentice mages are young people searching for strength in the arcane arts.
            </story>
			<description>Cast a cold eye, on life, on death, horseman, pass by</description>
            </magicapprentice>
            <thief>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>Rogues fend for themselves, looking for fights in which they dictate the terms. They’re the shadows in the night that remain unseen until the right moment comes to strike. Rogues are opportunistic thieves, bandits, and assassins, but there’s an unparalleled art to what they do.
            </story>
			<description>You're your own man. Don't let nobody bully you into doing something you don't wanna do!</description>
            </thief>
            <bandit>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>Bandits rove in gangs and are sometimes led by thugs, veterans, or spellcasters. Not all bandits are evil. Oppression, drought, disease, or famine can often drive otherwise honest folk to a life of banditry.
            </story>
			<description>You seemed familiar, ain't  I killed you before?</description>
            </bandit>
        </level>
        <level value="2">
            <banditcaptain>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>It takes a strong personality, ruthless cunning, and a Silver Tongue to keep a gang of bandits in line. The Bandit captain has these qualities in spades.
            </story>
			<description>Wanted: Dead or Alive</description>
            </banditcaptain>
            <berserker>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>In battle, the berserkers were subject to fits of frenzy. They would howl like wild beasts, foamed at the mouth, and gnawed the iron rim of their shields. According to belief, during these fits they were immune to steel and fire, and made great havoc in the ranks of the enemy. 
            </story>
			<description>For some barbarians, rage is a means to an end – that end being violence</description>
            </berserker>
            <bard>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>Humming as she traces her fingers over an ancient monument in a long-forgotten ruin, a half-elf in rugged leathers finds knowledge springing into her mind, conjured forth by the magic of her song—knowledge of the people who constructed the monument and the mythic saga it depicts.
            </story>
			<description>One day, your grandchildren shall tell the tale of this moment</description>
            </bard>
            <magicmaster>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>After the mastery of magic, apprentices become self independent, well-learned magic participants.</story>
			<description>A little bit better fireball</description>
            </magicmaster>
        </level>
        <level value="3">
            <magicgrandmaster>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>The greater honor comes as the magic master earns himself with the capability of serving the royal family. Doing such honorable job makes them famous during the students who have a desire for magic. 
            </story>
			<description>Greatest honor</description>
            </magicgrandmaster>
            <witch>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>Witches are a type of wizards and almost all of them are female.</story>
			<description>Destruction for good</description>
            </witch>
            <assassin>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>Assassins spent their lifetimes engaged in spy missions, some involving spending months or even years in hostile territory. The aim was to gather crucial information, and return to their spymasters or employers with intel that could change the fate of worlds.
            </story>
			<description>Shadow Spellcasters</description>
            </assassin>
            <catapult>
			<race>weapon</race>
			<story>Nearly all catapults employed in ancient and medieval artillery operated by a sudden release of tension on bent wooden beams or of torsion in twisted cords of horsehair, gut, sinew, or other fibers. An exception was the medieval trebuchet, powered by gravity.
            </story>
			<description>Only a lever can do it</description>
            </catapult>
        </level>
        <level value="4">
            <cultist>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>Cultists swear allegiance to dark powers. Most conceal their loyalties to avoid being ostracized, imprisoned, or executed for their beliefs. Unlike evil acolytes, cultists often show signs of insanity in their beliefs and practices.
            </story>
			<description>Serve in dark hours</description>
            </cultist>
            <priest>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>Priests are common units inside a church, from where they preaching the highest One’s goodness and travel to other nations for missionary.</story>
			<description>For the highest One</description>
            </priest>
            <bloodwitch>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>Blood witches are powerful witches who specialize in the use of blood magic. They are known to chant and perform blood rituals.
            </story>
			<description>Desire… more blood</description>
            </bloodwitch>
            <darkknight>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>The Dark Knights were once the proud Silver Knights of Cinder Lord. Long ago they fought chaos demons and were charred black. Many traveled with Cinder Lord to the First Flame, and were burned to ashes when he linked the First Flame. 
            </story>
			<description>Silence...</description>
            </darkknight>
        </level>
        <level value="5">
            <magebelial>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>Grand Master Mage Belial is one of the most powerful mages living in the ancient kingdom Hammord. He serves the king as a magic consultant and provides strategies against dark beings.
            </story>
			<description>For the Empire! For the Lion!</description>
            </magebelial>
            <royalinquisitor>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>The Empire crashes its enemies in the battlefield. However, sometimes it requires special personnel  to carry secret missions so that the destruction of its hidden rebels is inevitable.
            </story>
			<description>In darkness waiting for glory to come</description>
            </royalinquisitor>
            <shadowfran>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>Not everyone believes the power of shadow, but Fran has become so mush towards darkness that the shadow itself replaces his body at one night. From that on, he have been the shadow.
            </story>
			<description>See me in the moon</description>
            </shadowfran>
            <cardinaleriri>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>There is a wealthy kingdom sits aside the far east. After its discovery, the church sends out its priests trying to convert it. However, after the transfer of this kingdom’s religion, there comes a Cardinal Eriri, who fights for independence from the origin church. And now it is he who controls this kingdom instead of the old king.
            </story>
			<description>Super religion political power</description>
            </cardinaleriri>
        </level>
    </normal>
    <hero>
        <level value="1">
            <robinhood>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>A legendary outlaw hero.</story>
			<description>By the bare scalp of Robin Hood's fat friar, This fellow were a king for our wild faction!</description>
            </robinhood>
        </level>
        <level value="2">
            <tatenoyousya>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>Emotionally unmoved, being a strong man means knowing the situation and protecting who you love and yourself.
            </story>
			<description>No! At least not this time...</description>
            </tatenoyousya>
        </level>
        <level value="3">
            <jinjyamiko>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>A courageous shrine lady doing her best to protect the town from youkai and other evils.
            </story>
			<description>Biu!</description>
            </jinjyamiko>
        </level>
        <level value="4">
            <orchestraleader>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>A common leader working in a random national orchestra.
            </story>
			<description>μ’sic forever!</description>
            </orchestraleader>
        </level>
        <level value="5">
            <cinderlord>
			<race>human</race>
			<story>Once a normal person but some day became chosen.
            </story>
			<description>To link the fire</description>
            </cinderlord>
        </level>
        <level value="6">
            <andrethehero>
            <race>human</race>
			<story>A legend.
            </story>
			<description>...</description>
            </andrethehero>
        </level>
    </hero>

</enemy>
</character>